I just replayed Dragon Age: Origins with so many mods
and I'm about to spoil the entire thing. But lucky for you every playthrough is different
And I promise you that your playthrough was completely different from mine.
Dragon Age: Origins was built by a famous developer from a country I can't even pronounce
and published by these loveable bastards.
It starts with an intro that tells the backstory.
It's like four minutes long. I think I can tell it faster:
So there are these fellas called the Darkspawn.
One day they decided to attack the world, and they became a rather major annoyance.
A guy named Carinus wanted to join them, but they said "No you can't because you're not a barbaric demon."
So Carinus responded "Okay, whatever, I'mma must start my own Darkspawn called the Grey wardens."
He recruited a bunch of warriors and they crushed the Darkspawn.
Now it's 400 years later and the Darkspawn are back!
But there's only like 12 wardens or something. 13 if you count Paul.
Don't. He's an alcoholic.
That's pretty much the entire intro. Like many other RPGs, we now get to create our own character.
I made a human noble because otherwise you have to be surrounded by a bunch of wankers and losers.
I also named him Friskies.
After the cat food.
Don't know why.
So the game starts and you're at this castle with your father and this guy is visiting.
They talk about how the Darkspawn has shown up, and some war they used to be in
There's also a guy named Duncan there, he's trying to recruit people to the Grey Wardens through a very personal approach.
Their first idea was a talent show, but too expensive.
So Friskies is there with his family, they have all gathered around and everything is great.
"I got top grades," "I just made that huge sale," "I'm pregnant."
"Aha, can you guys believe it's Christmas tomorrow?"
"Also, this is like the opening of every revenge movie ever."
Friskies goes to bed, and when he wakes up his entire family has been slaughtered by this guy.
Duncan shows up and he's like "Sadly your entire family is dead. I couldn't help them because...
...earmuffs. But do you want to join the Grey Wardens?
And Friskies, who has the superpower to talk without ever moving his lips, responds:
"Yeah, sure."
So Friskies and Duncan travel to Ostagar. It's a castle where they have decided to fight the Darkspawn.
The first person they meet is actually the king of the entire nation.
"Oh hello Duncan, is this your new recruit?" "My entire family is dead."
"Ah, he's a clown." "All of them."
"This guy, am I right?"
"Before you can join Grey Wardens, we have to test you."
"You and these completely wasteable NPCs are going to go into the forest and collect Darkspawn blood."
"Also, this is Alistair. He's going to join you ."
"Are you like my funny sidekick?" "I am."
"Fantastic."
So you travel into the forest to kill some Darkspawn.
Like most RPGs you get XP and levels; when you level up you get attribute points.
I never invested in strength or dexterity.
Never needed them in real life, won't need them here. I put all my points in cunning.
This is a Warden ready for the 21st century.
So they go out and collect the Darkspawn blood.
They also need to collect a paper that has important plot information on it, but this chick is hiding it.
Hi. I'm Friskies. Nice weather, huh?
"My name is Morrigan. I understand you want your paper. Well, you can't have it."
"'Kay. We'll leave."
"What?"
"Did you get the paper like I asked you?"
"Oh! Didn't hear that part."
"Was wearing earmuffs."
So they perform a ritual that requires recruits to drink Darkspawn blood before they can join.
The expendables die, and Friskies survives. What a surprise.
Now the wardens have to go to a strategy meeting with the king.
"I'm going to win this and get all the glory."
"No, you won't. I'm going to betray you."
"I will have a victory parade every year."
"No, you'll be dead after I betray you."
"The Grey Wardens will be there and everything will be great."
"I... give up."
Friskies, Alistair, expose-able mage and Friskies's dog have a mission to clear the tower.
They do this the tower, gets overcrowded, and surprise surprise Loghain, this guy, betrays the king.
They wake up a couple of days later in Morrigan's house.
"Okay, a quick rundown: Loghain betrayed king and blamed us. We are now wanted criminals. You are now the leader of the Grey Wardens, congratulations. Important plot paper that Duncan wanted contains treaties with different nations and they have to fight for us. We have to travel to these nations and sort of show them this paper. Also to a city called Redcliffe, I was raised there, and they will fight for us. Also I'm the brother of the former king. Did you get all that?"
"Yes. Let's go!"
"Take Morrigan with ya."
"What!?"
"'Kay."
So now the game actually starts!
First we talk to a city called loitering. It's a city. That's about to be brutally destroyed here. You meet Liliana. She's a new companion
bonjour I am an alien from the
[le] [Chien] [Empire], are you sure you not from [France] no only famous for
Targets and uh
Typhus towel and all tine well I guess [star] wine would be call. [it's] the same thing
I am from [olay] also when you leave the city you see this guy in a cane
So you're locked up you innocent - what no why murdered eight people and feasted on [their] corpses?
What the fuck why it was just a prank, bro?
Well, then all is forgiven when I joined me in kids in Darkspawn. [no] fine. Then here. We have the world map
You can travel anywhere and between travels you can stay at this temp and spend time with your companions
You can even hit [on] them and build a romantic relationship
Personally never got it work
Hey Morgan are there 20 letters in the alphabet [in] the majors alphabet or in the theatres common alphabet?
Oh, I guess I forgot. You are [a] cutie
What friskies needs to meet your the fred cave in Red Cliff where a lizard grow house Town life?
Mostly great nice weather, we're getting a mini. Golf course are [are] my brother
He sick haven't seen him for months also every night our town gets [attacked] by the Walking Dead
So there's that [who] can I help sure help people around town, raise morale and defense?
So we go to this meeting gave [me] money
So [we'll] help then you go to this guy and give him money
So he'll help then you go to this guy and give him money
So he'll help money the best solve our problems since twelve thousand BC
You stay there and at [night] [lease] [on] base [attacked] the city you fight them, but they go down way too easy turns out
They're all paper mache and on a string it was old man murder
He was trying to scare away tourists, so he could build a coal mine, and he would have gotten away with it, too
if it weren't for those meddling wardens
Thanks for the help [now]. We can go to the castle and check on my brother, [Dr]
Friskies and the Gang goes to the castle, so they are least not sick. He's in a coma watch. Why what happened?
Have you ever heard of auto-erotic asphyxiation?
Well anyways, there's a way to wake him up
do you know the prophet of our religion Ondraw state well when she died he was cremated and
I could you go find her ashes so that the earl can eat them?
So friskies travels to the elves to see if they won't help what yeah, [we're] totally in bro. I love the two towers
I've only seen [the] hobbit movies what though fuck okay new deal
We have a werewolf problem. Did I create that where [we'll] problem. I don't know do you care. I don't care fix that
Second thing you have to watch the original trilogy. I have them all on vhS special edition
You can borrow them, but you have to rewind [I] didn't really want to fight werewolves
They cannot scare me so I decided to go for the ashes instead
So I [travelled] to the place where the ashes were supposed to be
To get to them [you] have to answer this question these sort of riddles to prove that you are worthy
First question who almost spooky ghosts are you scared not really?
Okay, second question boo look at my eyes. How spooky aren't they huh? I mean not, really oh
Come on. You're a bit spooked. [I] am not. Oh come on no fine
take the Ashes and charge back to the yard [he] tells you that he will summon the lance meet with all the [lords] so they
Can take down the [gang] after you have Gathered all the armies [he] also needs a belt for some unspecified reason
So [we] travel back to the elves and you face the wolves and it turns out. They just want to talk hello
I am the spirit of the wolves yelp's are actually the evil ones if you let me explain
I am on your side now what why this keeps happening? You meet the old theater upstairs and he agrees [to] talk
That's what she looks like that's bullshit, bro
We can't compete with [that] to reverse the curse of these wolves you have to sacrifice yourself else later fine
I'll sacrifice myself but first there's something that needs to be done looks really boring to be honest, shut up
You know what movie I really liked the teenage Mutant [Ninja] Turtle movie Jesus Christ
I was I was actually worried about sacrificing myself now
I just want to go they travel to the wars they get to the war town, so this is nice
[they] got the Lava and [the] statues yeah, yeah, this is so uncomfortable
Yeah, I know. I'm so worried about seeing something offensive. You know, what [allister] screw it. Let's let's get out of here
Let's not recruit the wharfs. Let us grind to max level still need a companion though. You know because bioware game hey you oh
Wanna Join us. We're Gonna kill a dragon. [I] this was a good day
So you come to meet the mages here is where you scale a tower and face a bunch of demons that have been summoned on
one of the floors your entire party falls asleep because of this guy and you
Enter the fade where the demons and the Darkspawn come from very cool interesting idea
[I] play some of it
And I quickly [realized] [this] is the worst thing ever put in a video game [8] most and washed water surprise
So [mages] are in yay. Oh yay
the Wardens and the Gang Travel to the Capital City
Here is where the ark's land speed is being held to take down low game
They arrive way before the lands with actually starts
And it's you're supposed to travel around the city and Gather nobles and the support to take down low [game]
I did not I took this case - went to the tavern and got
Shit-faced [here's] the thing let's be honest Friskies has so much coming right now
He can probably convince the entire lands [meat] that he is a dinosaur the lands meat start
What do you accuse me of who do you think you are? Huh logan?
I'm not going to try to convince these people by debating let's battle fine
Rap battle huh yo. Yo. I'm piss kiss yo yo. Yo, okay. Okay? I give up [umm]
I'm not going to embarrass myself [alistair] becomes king or something and they get ready for the final battle with the Darkspawn
But there's a problem
Turns out only a Grey warden
Can kill a darkspawn dragon later or whatever they called and when they do they kinda Sorta die in [his] room frisk these fines Morrigan?
[Haymore] again, what is it friskies? You're not ready to face the Darkspawn Dragon Lord leader, okay?
[what] can I do to get ready?
well
Training montage
It's finally time for the big Battle hooray
So you kill a couple of demons the [dwarves] show up because they solve their own problems like adults
[risk] is not a stomach to Topple [tower] [to] face the dragon
They kill him with the help of [ballestas] then alistair sacrifices himself Willingly
[I] will not kill [the] dragon come on. No kill. It sacrifice yourself. I will not
Yo-yo, I'm friskies. Yo frisk is in the house. Yo
Dragons Dead this woman is lected King
but where did Friskies go we may never know if you're interested in Dragon age origins you should probably check out another review and
That's the kilian experience. Well. I hope you liked the video subscribe for more garbage and the next review [will] be
Dishonored down it should take two weeks as usual, but I'm thinking my computer is about to explode